<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partha Pratim Chatterjee on Home</title>
    <link>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partha Pratim Chatterjee on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 13:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One API to rule them all</title>
      <link>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 13:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/api/</guid>
      <description>To further assist &amp;lsquo;going to market&amp;rsquo; strategies, it is imperative from a technical standpoint to have an application interface to perform the proverbial &amp;lsquo;CRUD&amp;rsquo;. The interface should be platform agnostic and must integrate seamlessly to web interfaces, reporting tools such as Tableau or data custom data platforms
My current project is to build a collection of restful that can be consumed by above mentioned platforms.
Architecture Decisions  One monolithic application over microservices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extract, Transform and Load: Parsing EDI Claims</title>
      <link>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/parser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/parser/</guid>
      <description>In order to improve the data ingestion strategies, I engineered a client agnostic data parser
 extracts information from industry standard EDI (Electronic data interchange) files load data to the corresponding client databases run transformations (calculations) on the extracted data  Architecture Decisions  a pluggable engine that is slient agnostic and cloud provider agnostic Implements a robust secret management paradigm Integrates with workflow management platforms such as Apache airflow A CI/CD pipeline to consume deployment triggers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready To Work: A covid Initiative</title>
      <link>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/ready_to_work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 12:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/ready_to_work/</guid>
      <description>In the current COVID hit world, it is necessary to understand wether employees are fit to go back to work. I developed a pluggable interface,
 that consumes a survey response in the form of json, queues it to our AI to calculate the odds for or against a person going back to work and sends out those results to a web screen  Architecture Decisions  One monolithic application over microservices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IaC Platform</title>
      <link>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/iac_platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/post/iac_platform/</guid>
      <description>In my experience, one of the key factors that influence a company&amp;rsquo;s velocity at whhich it can go to the market, is its ability to devise a platform that manages the infrastructure deployment of its clients.
In my current company, I had a similar task at hand, where i was to build a a cloud agnostic Infrastructure as Code platform (IaC Platform).
Architecture Decisions  Build a framework to import logically grouped modules (IaC module framework) Build a gateway to onboard clients seamlessly (IaC client framework) Version control infrasture and configuration states to facilitate incremantal updates  Tech Stack  Terraform to automate infrastrucutre deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chatter19.github.io/partha_pratim_chatterjee_portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media platforms.
   Platform URL     LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/parthapratimchatterjee786    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
